

export const data = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Kora?",
    "options": ["Mr. Dickson Nsofor", "Mr. Ukanwa Uzoma", "Mr. Cristiano Ronaldo", "Bishop David Oyedepo"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the main focus of Kora's solutions?",
    "options": ["E-commerce platforms", "Social media marketing", "Financial payments across Africa", "Supply chain logistics"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Kora product?",
    "options": ["Payment Links", "Virtual Accounts", "Card Issuance", "Grocery Delivery"],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What does Kora offer for businesses to accept payments online?",
    "options": ["Payment Links", "Settlements", "API References", "Mobile Money"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which feature allows Kora customers to get real-time balance and reconcile transactions?",
    "options": ["Instant Settlements", "Scheduled Settlements", "Bulk Payouts", "Balance"],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Where is Kora's fully operational UK office located?",
    "options": ["London", "Manchester", "Birmingham", "Edinburgh"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which payment method does Kora emphasize for businesses in Africa?",
    "options": ["Cash on delivery", "Mobile wallets", "Bank transfers", "Cryptocurrency"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What type of documentation is available for developers to explore Kora's solutions?",
    "options": ["API Documentation", "Guides", "Case studies", "All of the above"],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What does Kora prioritize to ensure secure payments for customers?",
    "options": ["Fast transactions", "User experience", "AML transaction monitoring", "Social media integration"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "How can businesses contact Kora for support and inquiries?",
    "options": ["Email", "Phone call", "Live chat", "All of the above"],
    "answer": 3
  }
];
